nissanusa.com 2014-12-31

# Nissan Privacy Policy | Nissan USA

We value your privacy.

Nissan North America collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site. Nissan North America is the sole owner of the information collected on this site (except that our subsidiary Nissan Motor Acceptance Corporation owns information collected from credit pre-approval applications). We will not sell or rent this information to others. We will only share this information with our affiliates and dealers, and marketing partners contracted to do business on our behalf (e.g., brochure fulfillment).

If you provide your Social Security Number to us, we will (1) Protect the confidentiality of Social Security numbers, (2) prohibit unlawful disclosure of Social Security numbers, and (3) limit access to Social Security numbers.

Nissan North America uses two types of user information: anonymous information gathered from cookies and log files, and personal information you provide us for certain services. See below for definitions of each of these methods.

(Effective October 1, 2008)

**Anonymous Information - Cookies and Log Files**

**Use of Nissan Websites**

By usage of Nissan websites and providing your personal information, you agree to the collection and use of your information as stated in this Privacy Policy. In addition to the uses and disclosures listed therein, Nissan may use third party providers to collect and record data on the use and performance of the Site during your visit (“Usage Data”), which may include without limitation the pages you view, the search terms you enter, your IP address, and personal information that you submit through the website. Usage Data may be collected by Nissan or its third party provider through “cookies”, log files and other technology. Nissan uses this information to administer the Site and to improve the services provided to you. Nissan may share information collected through the Site with suppliers to provide services for us or as required by law or court order. Nissan may also share Usage Data in an aggregate statistic format with a third party; such statistics would not include personal information. Nissan does not rent, sell, or trade Usage Data outside of Nissan.

Nissan does not respond to “do not track” beacons or other such signals. You may have received a tracking mechanism prior to your visit to the Site from other parties that will continue to track your activity while on the Site. Such data would be subject to the privacy policy of the other party from whom you received the mechanism, and we do not control or receive data from such mechanisms. For more information on how to opt-out of advertiser tracking mechanisms, please visit [www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to personal information, until a user provides that information (see below). If a user rejects or deletes the cookie, he/she may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, the user will not be able to receive notification of special offers, or participate in any contests that may take place. Cookies also enable us to track and aggregate clickstream behavior data. By doing this we can better target the interests of our users and enhance their experience on our site.

Nissan also maintains standard web logs that record data about all visitors to this Web site. These logs may contain:

  * The Internet domain from which you access this site.
  * Your IP address (Your computer is automatically assigned an IP address when you surf the Internet. Your IP address is either static or dynamic. A static IP address may be identifiable to you; a dynamic address is usually not identifiable to you).
  * The type of browser and operating system you use.
  * The date and time you visited this site.
  * The pages you viewed on this site.
  * The address of the Web site from which you linked.

Nissan uses web log and clickstream information to help us design our site, to identify popular site features and to make the site more useful for visitors. Web logs are recorded in sequential files, and we normally do not attempt to identify individuals from these logs. However, we may use web logs to identify persons attempting to break into, disrupt, or damage our Site. We may share web log information with law enforcement personnel if we believe evidence exists, or is likely to occur, of a violation of federal, state or local laws or regulations.

Nissan advertising at other non-Nissan sites may be serviced by Nissan service providers, who may use cookies to collect information about your visits to those sites. Information collected may include the pages visited, date and time, browser information and/or IP address. We normally make no attempt to link this information to you personally, except under circumstances described above. This information is gathered in order to help us customize and target our advertising to the needs and interests of our customers. If you wish to opt out of this tracking at our advertising at third party sites, please visit the following sites:

**BACK TO TOP**

**Volunteering Personal Information**

Users may choose to volunteer personal information (name, e-mail address, phone number, etc.) in order for us to provide them with services such as brochure and information requests, surveys and contests, site announcements, and special offers at the time of the request or in the future. If you would like to have your e-mail address removed from our list, click the [“ _ _unsubscribe__ ”](http://www.nnainfo.com/email/unsubscribenissan.aspx?x=H699) link and enter your e-mail address. Or you can call or send regular mail to remove yourself from the list (see contact information below).  

Nissan does not sell or rent user information to any third parties. We share user information with our affiliates and dealers, and marketing partners contracted to do business on our behalf (e.g., brochure fulfillment). When the user signs up for certain services and offers on our site, we will share names, or other contact information necessary for any associate third party to provide these services. Nissan will share user information in accordance with the privacy policy in effect at the time the information is collected.

If a user's personal information changes, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct or update that user's personal data provided to us. This can be done by e-mailing [privacy@nissan-usa.com](mailto:privacy@nissan-usa.com) or by contacting Nissan Consumer Affairs as outlined below.

**BACK TO TOP**

**E-mail a Friend**

If a user elects to e-mail a friend from this Web site, a function available from the Design Your Vehicle page, we ask for the friend's e-mail address. Nissan North America captures this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time e-mail.

**BACK TO TOP**

**Security**

Nissan takes all reasonable precautions to protect our users' information, both while the information is being transmitted and after it is received by us.

When our credit pre-approval form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with SSL 128-bit encryption software, an industry standard for reputable organizations. While on a secure page, such as our credit pre-approval application form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to unlocked, or open, when you are just "surfing." For more information on the Nissan Motor Acceptance Corporation (NMAC) privacy notice, see "NMAC Privacy Policy" below.

Furthermore, once the information has been received by us, we use security procedures and policies commensurate with industry standards to safeguard against loss, theft, unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification and disclosure. If you have any questions about the security of our Web site, you can send an e-mail to [privacy@nissan-usa.com](mailto:privacy@nissan-usa.com).

**BACK TO TOP**

**Links**

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Nissan North America is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each Web site that collects personal information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**BACK TO TOP**

**Notification of Changes**

We retain the right to change this privacy policy at any time. We will post those changes to this page so that users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. We will use, share, and disclose all information in accordance with the privacy policy in effect at the time the information was collected.

**BACK TO TOP**

**Certain Disclosures**

Nissan may disclose any data, whether personally identifiable or not, to any person performing audit, legal, operational or other similar services for Nissan. Whenever possible, we will require any recipient of personal information for these purposes to agree in writing to hold the information in confidence, to use the information only for the permitted purpose, and to return or destroy the information when the services are completed.

We may also disclose any data, whether personally identifiable or not, when required to do so by subpoena, court order, or warrant. Whenever feasible, Nissan will notify the effected user by e-mail that such disclosure will or has occurred.

We may also disclose any data, whether personally identifiable or not, when we reasonably deem it necessary to protect the safety of (i) an individual, (ii) the public, or (iii) the security and reliability of Nissan and/or this Web site.

**BACK TO TOP**

**Children**

Nissan does not knowingly allow anyone under the age of 13 to participate in any services offered on our Web site which requires the submission of user information. If we learn that a user is under 13 and has submitted user information to us, we will delete that information as promptly as possible.

**BACK TO TOP**

**Nissan Contact Information**

To contact Nissan online you may click on the "Contact Nissan" link below. To contact Nissan offline you can send mail to:

Nissan North America Consumer Affairs  
Attn. NissanUSA.com Privacy  
P.O. Box 685003  
Franklin TN 37068-5003

Or, during business hours, call 1-800-NISSAN1.

**BACK TO TOP**

**NMAC Privacy Policy**

FACTS | WHAT DOES NISSAN MOTOR ACCEPTANCE CORPORATION DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?  
---|---  
  
**Why?**

| 

Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.  
  
**What?**

| 

The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:

  * Social Security number and transaction history
  * Account balances and payment history
  * Purchase history and account transactions

When you are _no longer_ our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.  
  
**How?**

| 

All financial companies need to share customers' personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers' personal information; the reasons Nissan Motor Acceptance Corporation chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.  
  
Reasons we can share your personal information | Does Nissan Motor Acceptance Corporation share? | Can you limit this sharing?  
---|---|---  
  
**For our everyday business purposes -** such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus

| 

**YES**

| 

**NO**  
  
**For our marketing purposes -** to offer our products and services to you

| 

**YES**

| 

**NO**  
  
**For joint marketing with other financial companies**

| 

**YES**

| 

**NO**  
  
**For our affiliates' everyday business purposes -** information about your transactions and experiences

| 

**YES**

| 

**NO**  
  
**For our affiliates' everyday business purposes -** information about your creditworthiness

| 

**NO**

| 

**We don't share**  
  
**For nonaffiliates to market to you**

| 

**NO**

| 

**We don't share**  
  
Questions? | 

Go to [www.nissanfinance.com](http://www.nissanfinance.com/)  
  
---|---  
Who we are  
---  
  
**Who is providing this notice?**

| 

Nissan Motor Acceptance Corporation (NMAC) and Nissan-Infiniti LT (NILT), for whom NMAC acts as servicer.  
  
What we do  
---  
  
**How does Nissan Motor Acceptance Corporation protect my personal information?**

| 

To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.  
  
**How does Nissan Motor Acceptance Corporation collect my personal information?**

| 

We collect your personal information, for example, when you

  * apply for financing or apply for a lease
  * pay your bills or give us your contact information
  * pay us by check

We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.  
  
**Why can't I limit all sharing?**

| 

Federal law gives you the right to limit only

  * sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes - information about your creditworthiness
  * affiliates from using your information to market to you
  * sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you

State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing. See below for more on your rights under state law.  
  
Definitions  
---  
  
**Affiliates**

| 

Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.

  * Our affiliates may include companies with a Nissan or Infiniti name. Nissan and Infiniti dealers are not affiliates.

**Nonaffiliates**

| 

Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.

  * Nissan Motor Acceptance Corporation does not share with non-affiliates so they can market to you.

**Joint marketing**

| 

A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you. Our joint marketing partners include

  * Nissan dealers
  * Other financial institutions

Other important information  
---  
  
In California, NMAC does not share with Nissan dealers or other financial institutions for joint marketing, but does share with Nissan dealers so we can offer you incentives, discounts or bonus programs.  
  
**BACK TO TOP**

**Microsoft**

To view the Microsoft Privacy Statement and Terms of Use [click here.](http://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/fullnotice.aspx)

**BACK TO TOP**
